Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Iberian and Latin American Cultures, Honors Theses SC4-4581
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Iberian and Latin American Cultures, honors theses
1994-2011
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Department of Iberian and Latin American Studies
SC4-4581
1 Linear Feet (10 volumes in 3 boxes)
Honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Dept. of Iberian and Latin American Cultures.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of honors theses written by undergraduates in the Stanford University Dept. of Iberian and Latin American Cultures.
Access to Collection
The collection is open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. No photocopies may be made.
Acquisition Information
Theses were transferred to the Stanford University Archives from the Hume Writing Center in 2011.
Iberian Peninsula -- Study and teaching; Latin America -- Study and teaching; Student papers.; Stanford University. Department of Iberian and Latin American Studies
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2011-152
  - Schwartz, Elizabeth M., Reimagining democracy: television and women's movements in Latin America., 1997 (Box 1)
  - Urquidez, Cindy, Youth empowerment and community consciousness raising through cultural art., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Armendáriz, Rosa Linda, The transatlantic muses: re-membering Teresa de Ávila and Coyolxauhqui through a Chicana mysticism., 1997 (Box 1)
  - Márquez, Patricio, El curanderismo en Guadalajara: la lucha hacia una ortodoxia extraoficial., 1999 (Box 1)
  - Porter, Scott M., Desde su vuelta hasta su muerte: acción y reacción política de Miguel de Unamuno, 1930-36., 1994 (Box 1)
  - Shaw, Colleen, María Luisa Bemberg: La voz feminista y la mirada femenina., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Cordoba, Mark, The impositions of machismo in contemporary Mexico: a theoretical and sociological analysis., 1997 (Box 2)
  - Muñoz, José M., Hacia la bebida: la aculturacion del Mexico-Norteamericano., 1995 (Box 2)
  - Loera, Sandra, The sweatshop according to the costureras., 1997 (Box 2)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2018-060
  - Espinosa, Crystal, "Hacia un México más abierto al mundo: la descentralización del catolicismo en la literatura mexicana de los cincuenta", 2011 May (Box 1)